import 'dart:ui';
class Global {
  static int initialQuestion = 0;
  static int wonPrice = 500;
  static int randomColor = 0;
  static Color color = Color.fromRGBO(200, 164, randomColor, 1);
  static List<Map<String, String>> allQuestions = [
    {
      'question':
      "1. Which of these brand names also means \"one-billionth part of something\"?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Nano",
      'choice 2': "[B] Vista",
      'choice 3': "[C] Bolt",
      'choice 4': "[D] Sumo",
      'response': "A",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "2. Fields medal is a prestigious international honour given in which subject?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Life Sciences",
      'choice 2': "[B] Mathematics",
      'choice 3': "[C] History",
      'choice 4': "[D] Astronomy",
      'response': "B",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "3. Which of these is a non-renewable source of energy?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Solar power",
      'choice 2': "[B] Hydro power",
      'choice 3': "[C] Wind power",
      'choice 4': "[D] Natural gas",
      'response': "D",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "4. Which of these is a core ingredient of the south Indian dish Rasam?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Rajma",
      'choice 2': "[B] Brinjal",
      'choice 3': "[C] Cucumber",
      'choice 4': "[D] Tamarind",
      'response': "D",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "5. Which of these actors has not played the role of \"Devdas\" in a Hindi film?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Dilip Kumar",
      'choice 2': "[B] Shah Rukh Khan",
      'choice 3': "[C] Dev Anand",
      'choice 4': "[D] K L Saigal",
      'response': "C",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "6. Which unit of length derives its name from the Latin word for one twelfth part?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Yard",
      'choice 2': "[B] Feet",
      'choice 3': "[C] Inch",
      'choice 4': "[D] Metre",
      'response': "C",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "7. With reference to fashion and clothing what are loafers and sneakers types of?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Belts",
      'choice 2': "[B] Shoes",
      'choice 3': "[C] T-shirts",
      'choice 4': "[D] Sunglasses",
      'response': "B",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "8. What is the format of the world Kabaddi League broadcast on Sony Six?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Circular",
      'choice 2': "[B] Hexagonal",
      'choice 3': "[C] Rectangular",
      'choice 4': "[D] Triangular",
      'response': "A",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "9. Which is the single largest internal organ by mass in the human body?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Liver",
      'choice 2': "[B] Gallbladder",
      'choice 3': "[C] Kidney",
      'choice 4': "[D] Stomach",
      'response': "A",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "10. Indian-American business executive Arvind Krishna became the CEO of which American multinational technology company in 2020?",
    'choice 1': "[A] Oracle",
      'choice 2': "[B] Microsoft",
      'choice 3': "[C] Amazon",
      'choice 4': "[D] IBM",
      'response': "D",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "11. What is the Holy book of Islam?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Bible",
      'choice 2': "[B] BhagvathGeetha",
      'choice 3': "[C] MahaBharat",
      'choice 4': "[D] Khuran",
      'response': "D",
    },
    {
      'question':
      "12. What is the starting number of Gujarat's Pin code?",
      'choice 1': "[A] 5",
      'choice 2': "[B] 6",
      'choice 3': "[C] 7",
      'choice 4': "[D] 4",
      'response': "B",
    },
    {
      'question': "13. What dose the R stand for in RSS, the Hindu Organization?",
      'choice 1': "[A] Rashtriya",
      'choice 2': "[B] Rajkiya",
      'choice 3': "[C] Rajya",
      'choice 4': "[D] Rajniti2",
      'response': "A",
    },
  ];
}
